Artificial and Ephemera 060
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Martin Luther King, Jr. National Workshop and Rally for Justice and Peace - Martin Luther King, Jr. National Workshop and Rally for Justice and Peace, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Playgrounds - Playgrounds - Playgrounds, 1924-1941 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Playgrounds - Edgewood - Edgewood, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Playgrounds - Kenilworth - Kenilworth, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Playgrounds - Takoma Park - "Recreation" by Arthur Kriemelmeyer, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Playgrounds - Trinidad-Wheatley - Trinidad-Wheatley, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Playgrounds - Turkey Thicket - Turkey Thicket, 1930-1952 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Police Department - Police Department - Police Department, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Politics and Government - Politics and Government - Politics and Government, 1824-1951 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Politics and Government - 50th Anniversary of American Independence - 50th Anniversary of American Independence, 1826 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Politics and Government - 51st State Committee - 51st State Committee, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Politics and Government - "A Plan for Establishing a Model Government in the District of Columbia" - "A Plan for Establishing a Model Government in the District of Columbia", 1913-03-25 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Politics and Government - "Abstract of the Laws of the District of Columbia" by M. Thompson - "Abstract of the Laws of the District of Columbia" by M. Thompson, 1855 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Politics and Government - "Acts and Resolutions of the First Session of the First Legislative Assembly of the District of Columbia" - "Acts and Resolutions of the First Session of the First Legislative Assembly of the District of Columbia", 1871 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Politics and Government - Acts passed in 1830 Legislative Session - Acts passed in 1830 Legislative Session (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Politics and Government - "Address Before the Oldest Inhabitants' Association of Washington, DC by Mr. A. G. Riddle" - "Address Before the Oldest Inhabitants' Association of Washington, DC by Mr. A. G. Riddle", 1981 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Politics and Government - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners (ANC) - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners (ANC), 2003-01-02 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Politics and Government - Affadavit of Mr. F. B. Pustor (sp?) - Affadavit of Mr. F. B. Pustor (sp?), 1832-06-02 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  letter needs sleeved
- Politics and Government - Affairs in theDistrict of Columbia - Affairs in theDistrict of Columbia (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Politics and Government - Americanization of the People of the District of Columbia - "Americanization of the People of the District of Columbia" by Arthur Capper, 1940-08-13 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  Congressional record
- Politics and Government - Americanize Washington as a Wise Measure of War Preparedness - "Americanize Washington as a Wise Measure of War Preparedness" by Theodore W. Noyes, 1917-04-27 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Politics and Government - "An Act Providing for the Recording of Deeds, Mortgages, and othe Conveyances Effecting Real Estate in the District of Columbia" - "An Act Providing for the Recording of Deeds, Mortgages, and othe Conveyances Effecting Real Estate in the District of Columbia", 1878-04-29 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Politics and Government - "An Act Pespecting the Police of the District of Columbia" - "An Act Pespecting the Police of the District of Columbia", 1802-04-26 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Politics and Government - Appropriations for theGovernment of the District of Columbia - Appropriations for theGovernment of the District of Columbia, 1952-06-30 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Politics and Government - Board of Alderman - Board of Alderman, 1868-10-26 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Politics and Government - Board of Public Welfare - Board of Public Welfare, 1944-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Politics and Government - Board of Elections - Board of Elections, 1956-12-31 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Politics and Government - City Council - City Council, 1991-2001 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Politics and Government - Commissioner/Mayor Adminstrative Instruction - Commissioner/Mayor Adminstrative Instruction, 1972-1979 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Politics and Government - Commissioner/Mayor Adminstrative Instruction - Commissioner/Mayor Adminstrative Instruction, 1972-1979 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Politics and Government - Constitutional Status of the District of Columbia, The - Constitutional Status of the District of Columbia, The, 1910-06-25 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Politics and Government - Correspondence - From Office of Commishioner of Public Buildings, 1823-09-08 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Politics and Government - Correspondence - To Board of Alderman, 1826-1830 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  manuscript - Need rehoused
- Politics and Government - DC Statehood Coalition - DC Statehood Coalition, 1987-1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Politics and Government - DC Statehood Commission - DC Statehood Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Politics and Government - DC Statehood Compact Commission - DC Statehood Compact Commission, 1982-1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Politics and Government - DC Statehood Party - DC Statehood Party, 1981-1989 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Politics and Government - DC Vote - DC Vote, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Politics and Government - D.C. Wise Guide, The - D.C. Wise Guide, The, 1993-1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Politics and Government - District Half-and Half System - District Half-and-Half System, 1914-01-03 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Politics and Government - District of Columbia, The - "District of Columbia, The" by Henry E. Davis, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Politics and Government - District of Columbia Human Rights Act of 1977 - District of Columbia Human Rights Act of 1977, 1991-01 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Politics and Government - District od Columbia Self-Government and Governmental Reorganization Act - District od Columbia Self-Government and Governmental Reorganization Act, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Politics and Government - District Unemployment Compensation Board - District Unemployment Compensation Board, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Politics and Government - Election Laws - Election Laws, 1961-1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Politics and Government - Elections and Voting - Elections and Voting, 1949-1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Politics and Government - Forty Years of the District - "Forty Years of the District" by Henry B. F. Macfarland, ca. 1925 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Politics and Government - Free DC - Free DC, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Politics and Government - Government of the District of Columbia - "Government of the District of Columbia" by W. O. Owen, 1913 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Politics and Government - Handbook: The Juvenile Court - Handbook: The Juvenile Court, ca. 1954 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Politics and Government - Home Rule - Home Rule, 1969-1985 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Politics and Government - Home Rule Act - Home Rule Act, 1973-12-24 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Politics and Government - In Council (Proceedings) - In Council (Proceedings), 1873-06-03 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Politics and Government - Invisible Government at Washington, The - "Invisible Government at Washington, The" by A J. McKelway, 1913-09-20 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Politics and Government - Laws Relating to the Taxation of Personal Property in the District of Columbia - Laws Relating to the Taxation of Personal Property in the District of Columbia, 1916 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Politics and Government - League of Womes Voters - Committee Studing Alternatives to I-95 Lacks a Definite Role, 1973-01-24 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Politics and Government - Legislation - Legislation (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Politics and Government - Legislation - Bill to Amend and Continue in Force the Act to Incorporate the Inhabitants of the City of Washington, 1840-06-25 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Politics and Government - Let's Set Washington Free - "Let's Set Washington Free" by Alfred Steinberg, 1953-07 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Politics and Government - License Regulations of the Distric of Columbia - License Regulations of the District of Columbia, 1872-1882 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Politics and Government - List of Principal Municipal Authorities of the City of Washington, Georgetown and the District of Columbia - List of Principal Municipal Authorities of the City of Washington, Georgetown and the District of Columbia, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Barry, Marion, 1979-1997 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Berret, James G., ca. 1858 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Blake, James H., 1814-12-29 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Bowen, Sayles J., 1868-1869 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Bradley, William, 1835-02-18-1838-04-08 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Brent, Robert, ca. 1812 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Force, Peter, 1826-1832 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Gales, John, 1820-1829 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Lenox, Walter, 1851-1852 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Magrender, William B., 1856-08 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Mausy, John W., 1853-04-15 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Orr, Benjamin G., 1818-11-04 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Seaton, William W., 1841-1849 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Smallwood, Samuel, 1814-01-06 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Towers, John T., 1851-1856 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Van Ness, John, 1830-1832 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Wallach, Richard, 1865 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Politics and Government - Mayor - Weightman, Roger C., 1826-1841 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Politics and Government - Memorial of a Convention of Delegates, Suggesting Amendments to the Charter of the City of Washington - Memorial of a Convention of Delegates, Suggesting Amendments to the Charter of the City of Washington, 1844-04-17 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Politics and Government - Message from the President of the United States Accompanying a Memorial and Letter from the Commissioners of the City of Washington to the President - Message from the President of the United States Accompanying a Memorial and Letter from the Commissioners of the City of Washington to the President, 1802-01-11 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Politics and Government - Message of the Governor of the District of Columbia - Message of the Governor of the District of Columbia, 1874-05-12 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Politics and Government - Message of the Governor of the District of Columbia to the Third Legislative Assembly - Message of the Governor of the District of Columbia to the Third Legislative Assembly, 1873 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Politics and Government - Mr. Pitkin's Speech on the Loan Bill - Mr. Pitkin's Speech on the Loan Bill, 1814 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Politics and Government - New Deal Sound Mazuma - New Deal Sound Mazuma, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Politics and Government - Orders and Resolutions - Orders and Resoulutions (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Politics and Government - Organic Acts - Organic Acts, 1872-1914 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Politics and Government - Petitions - Petitions, ca. 2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Politics and Government - Petitions - Fund for Thomas Jefferson, 1826-07 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Politics and Government - Petitions - Petitions for Writ of Centiorari Claming Primary Jurisdiction for the Redress of Grievances Under the First Amendment of the United States Constitution in Certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia and to the United States District Court for the District of Columbia, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Politics and Government - Plunderers of Washington, The - "Plumbers of Washington, The" by Robert Wickliffe Woolley (Box 29, Folder 12)
  from Pearson's Magazine
- Politics and Government - Political and Social Conditions - Policical and Social Conditions (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Politics and Government - Political Development of the District of Columbia, The - "Political Development of the District of Columbia, The" by Henry E. Davis, 1899-12-29 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  published in the Proceedings of the Washington Academy of Sciences
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Bolden, A. Scott, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Brazil, Harold, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Cafritz, Peggy Cooper, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Chavous. Kevin (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Childs, Robert (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Clarle, Dave, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - DC Democracy Advocates, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Graham, Jim, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Gray, Vincent, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  writen in chinese
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Gurley, Calvin, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Hobson, Julius, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Lovell, Malcolm (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Norton, Eleanor Holmes, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Rice, Bill (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Schwartz, Carol, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Smith, Frank, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Politics and Government - Political Memorabilia - Tenant Assistance Program (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Politics and Government - Political Parties - DC Statehood Party, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Politics and Government - Political Parties - Democratic Party, 1884-12-18 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Politics and Government - Political Parties - Republican Party, 1924-1953 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Politics and Government - Political Parties - "Republican Party: Its History, Its Achievements", 1952 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Politics and Government - Proceedings of Legislative Council and Attached Building Regulations - Proceedings of Legislative Council and Attached Building Regulations, 1872 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Politics and Government - Proposal to Americanize the District of Columbia - Proposal to Americanize the District of Columbia (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Politics and Government - Reciepts - Court (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Politics and Government - Reference Book of the United States - "Reference Book of the United States, The" by Edmund F. Brown, 1841 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Politics and Government - Removal of the Capital - Removal of the Capital, 1804-1932 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Politics and Government - Removal of the Capital - How the Capitol of the United States came to be Located on the Banks of the Potomac, 1908-01-18 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Politics and Government - Removal of the Capital - "Nation and It's Capital, The" by L. U. Reavis, 1883 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Politics and Government - Removal of the Capital - "National Capital Movable, The" by L. U. Reavis, 1871 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Politics and Government - Removal of the Capital - "Removal of the National Capital", 1871-03-03 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Politics and Government - Removal of the Capital - "Report of Committee of the Columbia Historical Society" by A. R. Spofford, 1899-12-07 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Politics and Government - Removal of the Capital - Reorganization Plan No. 3 of 1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Politics and Government - Reports - Report to Superintendent of the City of Washington from Surverior's Office, 1815-10-09 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Politics and Government - Rules of Order - Rules of Order (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Politics and Government - Rules of Order of the Board of Alderman - Rules of Order of the Board of Alderman, 1859 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Politics and Government - Speech of Hallet Kilbourn - Speech of Hallet Kilbourn, 1872 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Politics and Government - Speech of Honerable George W. Hendee of Vermont - Speech of Honerable George W. Hendee of Vermont, 1876 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Politics and Government - Speech of Honorable William W. Crapo of Massachusetts - Speech of Honorable William W. Crapo of Massachusetts, 1876 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Politics and Government - Statehood - Statehood, 1972-1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Politics and Government - Statements and Reciepts - Statements and Reciepts, 1822-1830 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Politics and Government - Statements of Work, 3rd Ward - Statements of Work, 3rd Ward, 1822 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Politics and Government - Suffrage for the District of Columbia - Suffrage for the District of Columbia, 1940-11-19 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Politics and Government - Ten Miles Square Club - Ten Miles Square Club (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Politics and Government - The Day, November 8, 1938 - The Day, November 8, 1938, 1938-11-08 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Politics and Government - Voter's guide - Voter's Guide, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Politics and Government - Washington, A Model City - "Washington, A Model City" by William V. Judson, 1911-12-14 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Politics and Government - Washington City Government - Washington City Government (Box 30, Folder 20)
  from Political Science Quarterly
- Politics and Government - Watergate Scandal - Watergate Scandal, 1973-08 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Politics and Government - Your Washington - Your Washington (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Population - Census Schedules - Census Schedules, ca. 1910 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Population - Population Statistics - Population Statistics, 1930-1960 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Population - Population Statistics - 1936, 1936-08-21 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Population - Population Statistics - 1970 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Population - Population Statistics - 1977, 1978-10 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Population - Population Statistics - 1978, 1979-04 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Population - Population Statistics - 1980 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Population - Population Statistics - 1990 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Population - Population Statistics - 1992 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Presidents in Washington - Jackson, Andrew - Jackson, Andrew, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- Presidents in Washington - Roosevelt, Franklin D. - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1943-1946 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Prisons and Reformatories - Prisons and Reformatories - Prisons and Reformatories, 1862-1947 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Prohibition and Temperance - Prohibition and Temperance - Prohibition and Temperance, 1835-1927 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Prohibition and Temperance - Amending the District of Columbia Alcoholic Beverage Control Act - Amending the District of Columbia Alcoholic Beverage Control Act, 1940-05-08 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Prohibition and Temperance - Hercules Hoover to Cleanse Augean Washington - Hercules Hoover to Cleanse Augean Washington, 1929-10-05 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  from the Literary Digest
- Prohibition and Temperance - Progress - Progress, 1952-06 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Prohibition and Temperance - "Sober Appeal, by Temperance League No. 1, to the Thinking People and Voters of Washington, A" - "Sober Appeal, by Temperance League No. 1, to the Thinking People and Voters of Washington, A", 1854-05-01 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Real Estate - Facts about Washington's Real Estate Market - Facts about Washington's Real Estate Market, ca. 1967 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Real Estate - Legislation - Legislation, 1931-1935 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Real Estate - Legislation - Legislation, 1937-1940 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Residential Sections - Adams Morgan - Adams Morgan, 1958-04-18 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Residential Sections - Adams Morgan - "Adams Morgan: A New Concept in Community Planning and Social Progress" by W. Deaver Kehne, 1964-03-31 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Residential Sections - Adams Morgan - Adams Morgan Neighborhood Conference, 1960-05-18 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Residential Sections - Adams Morgan - Adams-Morgan News, 1959-1961 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Residential Sections - Adams Morgan - Experiment in Planning: Adams-Morgan, 1963-04 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Residential Sections - Adams Morgan - Soundings on Civic Affairs (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Residential Sections - Alexandria - Alexandria, 1887-1902 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Residential Sections - Bradley Hills - Suburbs Beautiful: Dedicated to Bradley Hills (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Residential Sections - Arlington Heights - Washington City and Arlington Heights (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Residential Sections - Brookland - Brookland and Me: I Like My Neighborhood Because (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Residential Sections - Capitol Hill - Capitol Hill (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Residential Sections - Chevy Chase - Chevy Chase, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Residential Sections - Cleveland Park - "Cleveland Park: An Early Residential Neighborhood of the Nation's Capital" by Grace Dunlop Peter, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Residential Sections - Columbia Heights - Columbia Heights, 1907-1915 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Residential Sections - Deanwood - Deanwood, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Residential Sections - Foxhall - Foxhall, 1942-11-15 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Residential Sections - Georgetown - Georgetown, ca. 1983 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Residential Sections - Georgetown - "Doorways and Dormers of Old Georgetown: A Historic Tour" by Alice Coyle Torbert, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Residential Sections - Glover Park - Glover Park, ca. 1977 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Residential Sections - H Street Area - "H Street Area Oral History Project" (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Residential Sections - Kalorama - "Waddy Wood in Kalorama: A Walking Tour", 1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Residential Sections - Kenilworth - "A DC Neighborhood by the Anacostia River, Kenilworth", 2006 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Residential Sections - LeDroit Park - LeDroit Park, 1881-01-11 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Residential Sections - Mount Pleasant - "The Story of Mount Pleasant and Milestones of its Later Day Development", 1923-01-08 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Residential Sections - Rock Creek Hills - "Live Along the Park - And Like It" (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Residential Sections - Southwest - Southwest, 1965-2005 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Residential Sections - Swampoodle - Swampoodle (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Residential Sections - Takoma Park - Takoma Park, 1923-1948 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Residential Sections - Takoma Park - "A Good Investment for Homes of Profit: The Villa Lots of Takoma Park, A Suburb of Washington City" by B. F. Gilbert, 1886 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Residential Sections - Takoma Park - "The Takoma Enterprise", 1930-1939 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Residential Sections - West End - West End, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Residential Sections - Woodley Park - Woodley Park (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Residential Sections - Woodley Park - "Woodley Park Community a Sketch of Our Past" by Madelyn Holmes, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Residential Sections - Woodley Park - Woodley Park Homes (Box 32, Folder 16)
  cox gift
- Restaurants - A. V. Ristorante Italiano - A. V. Ristorante Italiano (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Restaurants - Canton Chinese Cafe - Canton Chinese Cafe (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Restaurants - Capucino's Ristorante Italiano - Capucino's Ristorante Italiano (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Restaurants - Menus - Menus (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Restaurants - Old Ebbit Cafeteria - Old Ebbit Cafeteria, ca. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Restaurants - Restaurant Madrillon - Restaurant Madrillon (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Anacostia River, 1888-1956 (Box 32, Folder 23)